

QIANQIAN.W Visual Designer

(206) 953 0326 qianqiandesign@gmail.com qianqiandesign.com

STATEMENT

I am a designer with refined taste and absolute care for detail. I am curious to learn about the users and have empathy for their pain points. And I take great pride in my ability to think outside the box, and my attention to detail has resulted in improved user experience and greater performance.

EXPERIENCES

11/2019 - Now

Marketing Designer II

@ Evernote - Redwood City

- Led and developed large-scale campaigns and product launches, defined and expanded the campaign theme by initiating concept, presenting, and executing
- Created instructions and guidance for designers on the usage of creative resources, and introduced naming conventions as well as localization process for assets
- Developed scalable style guides, email templates and website component libraries to maintain consistency across the brand company wide
- Took initiatives on website refreshing, conceptualized and developed new treatment that drove market innovation and better website performance
- Supported brand storytelling across digital and print platforms, and worked closely
 with stakeholders to ensure branded content delivered on the brief, goals, and
 expectations

10/2019 - 11/2019

Senior UI/UX Designer

@ Leadvisor - San Jose

- Worked closely with the executive team to define the product vision that sets the direction and guides the product development team
- Created low-fidelity wireframes for the internal communications, designed dynamic and interactive prototypes, and turned team's ideas into testable artifacts

03/2018 - 09/2019

Product Designer

@ Jyve - San Francisco

- Collaborated with product managers and engineers to solve design problems and create flexible and scalable UI and UX solutions for mobile apps
- Interviewed the target user, built the user flows for the core product platforms
- Developed low-fidelity designs, wireframes, as well as highly functional and interactive prototypes, and created the necessary assets and graphic elements

05/2017 - 03/2018

Product Designer

@ Pillow - San Francisco

- Performed as a lead designer for marketing launch including banners, brochures, door hangers, email campaigns, presentation decks, iconography, and landing pages
- Worked with Engineer and Marketing team to design interaction and user interface for dashboard and responsive website

06/2015 - 06/2016

UI/UX Designer

@ KidzJet - San Mateo

- Developed pixel-perfect wireframe and mock-ups for KidzJet web-based dashboard and mobile application for both passenger and driver
- Participated in all phases of the product development lifecycle from ideation and definition to interface design, user research and testing

SKILLS

Figma HTML Animation CSS User Research Sketch Adobe Photoshop Interactive Design Sass Adobe Illustrator Javascript Speed Wireframing Adobe After Effect iQuery Concept Development Adobe Indesign Marketo Font-end Development

EDUCATION

09/2016 - 05/2019

Academy of Art University

Master of Art in Web Design & New Media

09/2013 - 06/2015

University of Washington, Information School

Master of Science in Library and Information Science